willful ignorance is when somebody know better and they keep doing a thing that you said you
don't like them to do right and you're just like you're exercising willful ignorance at this point
like you know that this is something that is gonna drive me crazy and you keep doing it and acting as
if you didn't know see that's the part that's the part the part where they act as if they didn't
know because listen people forget bad habits are hard to break right if you always been on some
weirdness and then you somebody's like hey i don't like that that's weird and you're like oh okay got
you but like you always been on some weirdness then it's gonna be tough for you to all of a
sudden be like cut the weirdness i get that but when someone brings it to your attention you'll
be like oh man i'm trying to shake that weirdness but i can't shake it i get it however when the
person acts like what are you talking about now we've we've stepped into the light of gas okay